A Guide to the Martha Baird Rockefeller Fund for Music records FA1420
Rockefeller Archive Center
Martha Baird Rockefeller Fund for Music records
1951-1987
1955-1982
Rockefeller Archive Center
Martha Baird Rockefeller Fund for Music
FA1420
139.43 Cubic Feet 359 letter-size document boxes, 2 index card boxes, 1 legal-size document box and 1 standard record storage box.
Arrangement
The Martha Baird Rockefeller Fund for Music collection is arranged in the following 13 series by file type:
Series 1: Project files
Series 2: Project files
Series 3: Board of Trustees Files
Series 4: Financial Material
Series 5: Publications and Printed Material
Series 6: Aid to Music Program
Series 7: Administrative records
Series 8: Photographs
Series 9: General Correspondence
Series 10: General Files
Series 11: Awards
Series 12: Project Card File
Series 13: Audio
Biographical / Historical
The Martha Baird Rockefeller Fund for Music was founded in 1957, as a private philanthropy, by Martha Baird Rockefeller with monies received from the estate of John D. Rockefeller Jr. Incorporated in 1962, the Fund's interest centered on young solo artists, who received support directly through individual grants or indirectly through contributions to performance organizations that offered advanced training and employment. Funds were also allocated to: aid symphony orchestras, opera companies, and other performing groups and organizations, including but not limited to the presenting of concerts to benefit local communities; to enable schools of music and other educational institutions to carry out programs and projects contributing to the training of students; to support festivals and other activities devoted to the advancement of musical knowledge and culture; and to establish or aid research in the field of musicology.
Until Mrs. Rockefeller's death in 1971, the Fund was supported by her contributions of $600,000 annually. Her will provided for an unrestricted bequest to the fund of $5,000,000, and the trustees elected to continue the program at the same level until funds were exhausted. The Fund was dissolved in 1982.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
This collection was donated to RAC in 1983. Record transfers began in the early 1980s and continued through 2005.
Scope and Contents
The vast majority of the collection is Project files for individual and institutional grant recipients and declinations. Project records often include applications, funding requests, grant actions, correspondence, and further background or supportive documentation.
The collection also contains a variety of policy and program records, meeting records, including dockets, agendas and minutes, correspondence, reports, printed material, and corporate and financial records including documents of incorporation and dissolution as well as budgets and financial statements.
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open for research with select materials restricted as noted. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC.
When requesting to view audiovisual material, please refer to the Title and the AV Number (example: AV 1916). Researchers are asked to check the "Restrictions" note for each Title. If a Title does not currently have an access copy, please contact a RAC archivist for further instruction.
In accordance with stipulations of the collecton agreemen - the project files on grants and declinations were unavailable for research until 1988. Administration files were unavailable for research until 2003.
- Project Files, 1955-1983; 1; 58.87 Cubic Feet 155 letter-size document boxes. Boxes 1-155.
  Arrangement
  Alphabetical by institutional name or by last name of grant/project recipient.
  - A-B-C-D
    - Abbate, Carolyn, 1973-1982 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Abeja, Rosalina, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Abel, Bruce, 1963-1966 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Abel, David Willard, 1962; 1966-1967 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Abernathy, Juandalynn, 1978-1979 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Abouchain, Maty, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Abramian, Sheryn, 1974-1982 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Abramovitz, David, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Abramowitsch, Miriam, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Abrams, Daniel, 1958-1962 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Abrams, Sheldon, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Abri, Minola Rabia, 1969-1973 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Academic Media, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Academia Monteverdiana, 1966-1968 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Accompanists, miscellaneous, 1970-1982 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Accurso, Francesca, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Acheson, David - Vital Issues, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Achterman, Nathan, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Ackerman, Anita, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Acosta, Adolovni, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Acord, Tom, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Acoustic Research Recording Project, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Adams, Arlene, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Adams, Armenta, 1959-1971 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Adams, Darrell, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Adams, David, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Adams, Elwyn, 1960-1961 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Adams, John, 1975-1978 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Adams, John C., 1975-1978 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Adams, John E., 1977 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Adams, John Kenneth, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Adams, Leslie, 1961; 1978-1982 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Adirondack Foundation, 1962-1972 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Adler, James, 1980-1981 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Adler, Murray (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Adler, Peter Herman (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Admon, Esther (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Adragna, Ignazia (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Adrian, Ara (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Aeolian Chamber Players (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Affiliate Artists, Inc. - Correspondence and Reports, 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Affiliate Artists, Inc., San Francisco, Opera Program (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Affiliate Artists, Inc. - Correspondence and Reports, 1968-1973 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Afro-American Music Opportunities Association, Inc. (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - After Dinner Opera Company (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Ahlouist, Janet (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Ahlstedt, Douglas (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Aibel, Howard (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Aiken, David (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Alaska Festival of Music (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Albanese, Maria (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Albany Institute of History and Art (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Albrecht, Johanna (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Albright Art Gallery (Buffalo, NY) (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Aldaz, Jose (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Aldwell, Edward (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Alexander, Ellen (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Alexander, Lynne (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Alexander, Mary M. (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Alford, Lamar (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Alicea, Mercedes (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Alimo, Ma Prem (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Allard, Maurice (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Allen, Betty (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Allen, Doris (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Allen, Gail Ann (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Allen, Judith (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Allen, Mary (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Allen, Mildred (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Allen, Richard (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Allers, Franz (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Alley, Edward L. (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Alonso, Virginia (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Alstadter, Judith (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Althouse, Paul (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Alton, William Lewis (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Amada, Kenneth (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Ambrose, Priscilla (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - American Academy in Rome (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - American Academy of Teachers of Singing (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - American Artists, Inc. (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - Akin-Pearl - Scott-Campbell, Sheila (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - American Artists Series -Joann Freeman Shwayder (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - American Baptist Convention (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - American Chamber Opera Emsemble (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - American Choral Foundation (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - American Conservatory Theatre (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - American Council of Emigres in the Professions, Inc. (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - American Council of Learned Societies (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - American Council for the Arts (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - American Culture Center (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - American Guild of Musical Artists (AGMA) (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - American Association of Museums (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - American Institute of Musical Studies (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - American Institute of Vocal Pedagogy (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - American International Music Fund (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - AMC - Financial Statements, 1957-1970 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - American-Korean Foundation (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - American Musicological Society (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - American National Opera Company (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - American National Theatre and Academy (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - American Opera Auditions (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - American Opera Center (Graf Mennin) (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - American Opera Society (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - American Opera Workshop of Vienna (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - American Orchestra for Contemporary Music, Inc. (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - American String Teachers (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - American Symphony Orchestra, Inc. (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - American Symphony Orchestra Leagude (ASOL) - General Correspondence, 1964-1968 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - American Symphony Orchestra Leagude (ASOL) - General Correspondence, 1955-1964 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - American Symphony Orchestra Leagude (ASOL) - Conductor Training, 1966-1970 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - American Symphony Orchestra Leagude (ASOL) - General Correspondence, 1971-1980 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - American Symphony Orchestra Leagude (ASOL) - String Program, 1962-1964 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - American Wind Symphony Orchestra, 1967-1968 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Amerika Haus (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Amerita Orchestra (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Ames, Richard (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Ammons, Rosalind (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Amorim, Sergio (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Amor, Musicae (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Amos, Gloria (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Anderson, Alfred (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Anderson, Arden Virginia (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Anderson, Donald (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Anderson, Donna K. (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Anderson, Linda C. (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Anderson, Raeder (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Anderson, Richard (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Anderson, Ronald (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Anderson, Rose (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Anderson, Ruth (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Anderson, Shari (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Anderson, Sylvia (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Anderson, Tommie Sue (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Ando, Katheryn (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Andrea, Soto (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Andreola, Howard (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Andrews, Donald (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Andrews, Doris (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Andrews, Joel (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Andrews, Theodora (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Andrix, George (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Andrulonis, Robert Edward (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Andrus, Robert (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Angeletti, Richard (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Angelini-Dolin, Tatiana (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Anguish, Elizabeth (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - Angwin, Jeff (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - Anievas, Agustin (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - An-Ming Wang (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - Anthony, Judith (Box 8, Folder 31)
    - Antico, Nancy (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Antonowicz, Ruslana (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Appel, William (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Arbizu, Ray (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Archer, Hal (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Arico, Fortunato (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Arlene, Bess (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Armstrong, Helen (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Armstrong, Louise (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Armstrong, Richard (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Armstrong, Ronald (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Arney, Arthur J., Jr. (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Arnholt, William (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Arnn, John David (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Arnold, David (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Arroyo, Martina (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Ars Antigua Society, Inc. (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Artesi, Jean (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Artists Advisory Council (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - Arts Council of Winston Salem (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - Arts Management (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - Arts Management Training Program (Duke University) (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - Artzt, Alice (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - Asaro, Josephine (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - Asch, Maedra (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - Aselford, Diedre (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - Asen, Simon - Orchestral Society of Westchester (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - Ashforth, Aiden (Box 9, Folder 28)
    - Aslanian, Richard (Box 9, Folder 29)
    - Aslanian, Vahe (Box 9, Folder 30)
    - Assa, Poli (Box 9, Folder 31)
    - Assali, Edoardo (Box 9, Folder 32)
    - Asselin, Andre (Box 9, Folder 33)
    - Associated Opera Companies of America, 1966-1971 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Association of American Colleges - Action Papers, 1960-1974 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Association of American Colleges - Financial Statements, 1960-1974 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Association of American Colleges - General Correspondence, 1960-1974 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Association of College and University Concert Managers (ACUCM) (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Associazione Lirica Concertistica Italiana (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Atherton, James (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Atkinson, David (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Atlanta String Quartet (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Ator, Mary (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Auer, Edward (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Auger, Arleen (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - August, Joan (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Aultz, Susanne (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Avery, James (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Ax, Emanuel (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Aybar, Francisco (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Ayyangar, Ms. Ranganayaki (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Babbitt, Milton (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Babikian, Virginia (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Baca, Richard (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Bachman, Bonita (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Bachman, Margaret (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Back, Robert (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Backus, Carolyn (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Bacon, Ernest (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Baer, Stephanie (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Bailey, Roberta (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Bailey, Therman (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - Bailiff-Bostaph, Nora (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Baker, Elaine (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - Baker, Edward (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - Baker, Guy Owen (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - Baker, Helen (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - Baker, Keith (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - Baker, Nancy K. (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - Baker, Polly Jo (Box 11, Folder 26)
    - Bala, Iris (Box 11, Folder 27)
    - Balada, Leonardo (Box 11, Folder 28)
    - Baldwin, Janice (Box 11, Folder 29)
    - Baldwin, Marcia (Box 11, Folder 30)
    - Balestrieri, Anthony (Box 11, Folder 31)
    - Ballard, Earline (Box 11, Folder 32)
    - Ballet Guild (Box 11, Folder 33)
    - Ballet Society, Inc. (Box 11, Folder 34)
    - Ballinger, Cathryn (Box 11, Folder 35)
    - Balogh, Endre (Box 11, Folder 36)
    - Baltimore Center for the Performing Arts, Inc. (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Baltimore Museum of Art (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Baltimore Opera Company (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Banat, Gabriel (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Bangor Symphony Orchestra (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Bank Street College of Education (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Banyak, Kalman (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Barfield, Louise (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Baraban, Susan (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Barba, Ernest (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Barber, Joan (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Barbieri, Saverio (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Barclay, Barbara (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Bar Harbor Festival (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Barker, Allen (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Barker, Sean (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Barkin, Elaine (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Barlow, Claire (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - Barnett, Cynthia (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Barnsley, Hedy (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - Barnum, Donald Curtis, Jr. (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - Barone, Diana (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - Barr, Albert E. (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - Barr, Bernie (Box 12, Folder 24)
    - Barrena, Carlos (Box 12, Folder 25)
    - Barrett, Arthur (Box 12, Folder 26)
    - Barrientos, Mario (Box 12, Folder 27)
    - Barron, David (Box 12, Folder 28)
    - Barron, Malita (Box 12, Folder 29)
    - Barry, Jerome (Box 12, Folder 30)
    - Barry, Robert (Box 12, Folder 31)
    - Bartee, Hermine (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Barthelson, Joyce (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Bartlet, M. Elizabeth (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Barrett, Herbert (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Bartlett, Carol (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Bartlett, Clifton M. (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Bartolini, Lando (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Barton, Jenneke (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Barton, Joan (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Bartos, Anna (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Basler, Kathleen (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Bath, Charles (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Battle, Robert (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Batson, Robert, Jr. (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Baty, Janice (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - Bauer, Carol (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Bauer, Therese (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Bauer-Mengelberg, Stefan (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - Bawden, Tana (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - Baxter, Carmelia (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - Baxter, Margaret (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - Bayard, Carol (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - Bay Chamber Concerts (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - Bayreuth Festival Master Classes (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - Bazemore, Raymond (Box 13, Folder 25)
    - Bazinet, Jacqueline (Box 13, Folder 26)
    - Becerril, Anthony (Box 13, Folder 27)
    - Beckwithh, David (Box 13, Folder 28)
    - Behan, Robert (Box 13, Folder 29)
    - Beattie, Herbert (Box 13, Folder 30)
    - Beaux Arts String Quartet (Gerald Tarack) (Box 13, Folder 31)
    - Beck, Mary (Box 13, Folder 32)
    - Bedford, Clark (Box 13, Folder 33)
    - Bell, Joseph - Bell Music Box (Box 13, Folder 34)
    - Bell, Paul (Box 13, Folder 35)
    - Bemko, Gregory (Box 13, Folder 36)
    - Bender, Col. George (Box 13, Folder 37)
    - Beni, Gimi (Box 13, Folder 38)
    - Beniades, Gloria (Box 13, Folder 39)
    - Bennett, David (Box 13, Folder 40)
    - Bennett, Elijah (Box 13, Folder 41)
    - Bennett, Robert (Box 13, Folder 42)
    - Bennette, George (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Berberian, Ara (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Bereck, Barton (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Bergey, Carol (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Berkshire Boy Choir (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Berkshire Music Center - String Symposium (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Berkshire Music Center - Music Theatre Project at Tanglewood (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Berkshire Music Center - Opera Department (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Berkshire Music Center - Opera Project 1957 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Berkshire Music Center, 1964-1965 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Berkowitz, Leo (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Berlitz School of Languages (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Berman, Edward W. (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Bernstein, Seymour (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Bernstein, Melvin, University of North Carolina (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Berquist, Dorothy (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Berse, Ellen (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Bessel, Annamaria (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Best, Richard (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Billions, Clifford (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Billotti, Paul (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Bilodeau, Leonard (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Bilson, Malcolm (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Binder, Peter (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Bird, Remson, DuBois (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - Birmingham, Hugh M., Indiana University (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Bishop, Dan Mahon (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - Bishop, Stephen (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - Bitar, Virginia (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - Blackmon, Henry, Jr. (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - Blackmur, Paula (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - Blair, Lynn F. (Box 15, Folder 22)
    - Blakeslee, Lynn (Box 15, Folder 23)
    - Blanchard, Barbara (Box 15, Folder 24)
    - Blanchard, Hayden Jr. (Box 15, Folder 25)
    - Blanchette-Berres, Estelle (Box 15, Folder 26)
    - Blanton, Joe (Box 15, Folder 27)
    - Bliss, Beverly (Box 15, Folder 28)
    - Bliss, Isle (Box 15, Folder 29)
    - Bliss, John (Box 15, Folder 30)
    - Bliss, Sharon (Box 15, Folder 31)
    - Block, Michael (Box 15, Folder 32)
    - Bloxam, Jennifer, 1982-1983 (Box 15, Folder 32A)
    - Blumfield, Coleman (Box 15, Folder 33)
    - Boatman, Donald (Box 15, Folder 34)
    - Boatwright, McHenry (Box 15, Folder 35)
    - Bodann, Carla (Box 15, Folder 36)
    - Bohen, Mary Louise (Box 15, Folder 37)
    - Boerner, Anna May (Box 15, Folder 38)
    - Bogart, Dorothy A. (Box 15, Folder 39)
    - Bogas, Roy (Box 15, Folder 40)
    - Bogoni, Paul (Box 15, Folder 41)
    - Bogue, Lawrence (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Bolman, Marcelle (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Bolton, Edwin (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Bolton, Helen (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Bomhard, Moritz (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Bonazzi, Elaine (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Booker, Bernice (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Boone, Betty Turner (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Borgeson, David (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Borletti, Bianca (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Bornstein, Peter (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Boruka, Shari (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Bosanko, Patricia (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Bosley, June (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Boston Comic Opera Company (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Boston Community Music Center (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - Boston Philharmonic Society (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - Boston Symphony Orchestra - Elliot Carter Concerto (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - Bottcher, Ron (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - Botti, Velia (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - Bourke, John (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - Bovbjerg, Helen (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - Bove, Lois (Box 16, Folder 23)
    - Bowdoin College (Box 16, Folder 24)
    - Bowens, Clifford (Box 16, Folder 25)
    - Bower, Beverly (Box 16, Folder 26)
    - Bowers, Jeanne (Box 16, Folder 27)
    - Bowers, Ann (Box 16, Folder 28)
    - Boyd, Denny T. (Box 16, Folder 29)
    - Boyden, John (Box 16, Folder 30)
    - Boydston, Margaret (Box 16, Folder 31)
    - Boyk, James (Box 16, Folder 32)
    - Boykan, Constance and David Abramovitz (Box 16, Folder 33)
    - Boyll, Lawrence (Box 16, Folder 34)
    - Bracali, Bretta (Box 16, Folder 35)
    - Bradel, Jean (Box 16, Folder 36)
    - Bradley, Brown (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Braidech, Sheila (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Brame, Grace (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Brand, Nathan (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Brandon, Sy (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Brandon, Theodora (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Brandowynne, Lois (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Brantley, Daniel (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Brass Quarterly (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Bratcher, James (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Braun, Matitiahu (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Brauner, Mitchell (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Bravos, Marion (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Brawner, Alpha (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Braxton, Walter (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - Breitbart, Margo (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - Brennan, Walter (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - Brevard Music Foundation - Action Papers (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - Brevard Music Foundation - Advisory Council (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - Brevard Music Foundation - Financial Statements (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - Brevard Music Foundation, Inc., 1957-1965 (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - Brevard Music Foundation, Inc., 1966-1975 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Brewer, Nadyne (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Brewer, Olivia (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Brewer, Virginia (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Brewster, Robert (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Brice, Carol (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Brickman, Miriam (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Bridge, Betsy (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Brieff, JoAnne (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Brienes, Harold (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Briscoe, James (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Britten, Dennis (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Britton, David (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Britton, Joyce (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Brobyn, Virginia (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Brockman, Thomas (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - Broderson, Margaret (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - Bronstein, Ena (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - Bronx House Music School (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - Brookbank, Richard L. (Box 18, Folder 20)